(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
Hololive Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
It's Ichijo Ririka!
I'm Mori Calliope.
ホロライブファンクラブ、始めました！
Hololive Fan Club has begun!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや、
Exclusive original goods, and...
チケット先行抽選。
...early ticket lotteries.
他にも楽しいコンテンツがいっぱい！
Lots of other fun content too!
Campaigns too? That sounds really fun. I'm curious.
さあ、みんな！ ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Come on everyone! Let's have fun together!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから、ずっと気になってたんだよね～！
I've always been curious about the open-air baths here!
…ね、キミも一緒に行かない？
...Hey, won't you come with me?
えっ！？ 一緒に入るって意味じゃないよ！？
Eh!? I don't mean entering together!?
おーそーじ！ モココ、大掃除をやってみたいんだよね！
Cle-an-ing! Mococo wants to try the big cleanup!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？
Of course you're doing it too!?
じゃあ、さっそく大掃除開始だー！
Well then, let's start the big cleanup right away!
え～？ 服のすきまがどうしたって～？
Eh~? What was that about the gap in your clothes~?
僕が掃除してる間に、
While I was cleaning, I wonder...
キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな～？
...exactly where you were looking~?
お～！ ここが夢にまで見た、日本の温泉街～♪
Oh~! This is the Japanese hot spring town of my dreams~♪
ん？ もしかして……
Hm? Could it be...
私と一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
...you're thinking you want to get in with me?
……いいよ、一緒に入ろっか……？
...It's okay, shall we get in together...?
…って、やばいやばい！ みんな、そろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
...Wait, oh no! Everyone, the countdown is starting!
5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!...
今年もよろしくお願いします！
...Please treat me well this year too!
えへへ…… なんかあらためてかしこまると、はずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... Being so formal is a bit embarrassing♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？ ほらほら！
Is it called Diamond Fuji? Look, look!...
だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えてきたよ！
...The outline of Mt. Fuji is becoming visible!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ～！
Somehow, just this scenery alone is moving~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！ つまみぐいしちゃだめだよ？
I'm going to make osechi! No snacking, okay?
もしつまみぐいしちゃったら……ガブってしちゃうからねっ！？
If you sneak a bite... I'll take a big chomp!
おめでとー！ おめでとー！
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!...
キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
...Celebrating while hugging you♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
Only Mococo can hug you!
ほらほらキミも、モココのことぎゅーっとして！
Come on, you hug Mococo too!
せーの！ 今年もよろしくお願いします！
One, two! Please treat us well this year too!
ホロライブ3期生
hololive 3rd Generation
次に挑む舞台は
The next stage they challenge is...
大作戦？
A big mission?
hololive 3rd Generation Live
#きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドルに推すしかないでしょ～
#Kyururun Big Mission: No Choice but to Support the Strongest Idols
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで あなたと作る大作戦！
Packing in "love" and "cute," a big mission to create with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
Full of everything until now, and a heart-pounding moment!
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする！
I feel like I can go anywhere!
ちなみに作戦の内容は
By the way, the details of the mission are...
とにかくかわいい！
Anyway, it's cute!
かわいいに満たされろ！
Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！
Mission in progress!
hololive production
hololive production COUNTDOWN LIVE 2025▷2026
FLOW GLOW
Justice
ReGLOSS
Advent
hololive Indonesia 3rd Gen
Secret Society holoX
Promise
hololive Indonesia 2nd Gen
Myth
hololive 5th Gen
hololive Indonesia 1st Gen
hololive 4th Gen
hololive 3rd Gen
hololive GAMERS
hololive 2nd Gen
hololive 1st Gen
hololive Gen 0
COUNTDOWN LIVE 2026
1st STAGE
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE
来年もよろしく！
Look forward to next year too!
Let's go!
搭載 V8 エンジン
Packin' a V8 engine
第七感持ってる言辞
And a seventh sense for things
Rock するこの世界と全人類
The world and all of humanity will be rocking
この5人で Game は Change
With us five, the game be changing
鳴る四輪 発射せよ
The four wheels roar, ready to launch
皆さんサンキュー サランヘヨ
Thank you all, I love you
操る二台のターンテーブル
Mastering two turntables
誇る一番 ここから 0
Taking number one, from ground zero
Hey, let's go out so get in the car
リスク超え挑戦
Take risks and challenge
チャンスもセットだ当然
Chances come naturally
昇り上げる Top End
Rising to the top end
座布団積んでいけ シャッペン
Stack the points and sharpen up
ぶち込め FG ROADSTER
Slam it in, FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊集合 能力者
Special forces gathering, ability users
この歴史に乗る ここから
Get on this history, from here
ぶっちぎりで 置き去りコンラクション
Breaking away, leaving them behind
今 高速で ぶち抜いていく 大気圏
Now, breaking through the atmosphere at high speed
エンジンからジェットの咆哮
The roar of the jet from the engine
入れてる 怪気炎
Fueled by a mysterious spirit
遥かに広がる 大地を超えていく
Beyond the far-reaching land
快気勢
With spirited vigor
バックミラーに ビックブルーが
The Big Blue is reflected...
映ってる I believe
...in the rearview mirror, I believe
I believe!
ファイヤー！
Fire!
ぶち上げたいから 飛んでいく
I want to pump it up, so I fly
宇宙ら世代
Cosmic generation
この燃料 朽ち果てない
This fuel will never rot away
銀河寿司食べたい
I want to eat galaxy sushi
見えてるデカいビジョン
Seeing a big vision
燃えてるメンバー一途
Members burning with devotion
ただいま現在進行形
Right now, in progress
超えていく世界規模
Surpassing global scale
叶うはずはマスター
Destined to come true, Master
心臓がモンスター
Heart is a monster
エリアはサタミナ
Area is Saturn
FG パーティーは
FG Party is...
光るテスラ・ロッサ
Shining Testarossa
ヘビーブースター 目覚めていく本能
Heavy booster, awakening instinct
蒼い炎
Blue flame
V-I-P Let's go out
So get in the car
0から宇宙まで とらわれず走る
Run from 0 to space, without being trapped
FG ROADSTER 唸るブースター
FG ROADSTER, roaring booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me!
Now, chase me!
ターボ搭載スーパーカー ハンドルさばきはシューマッハ
Turbo-equipped supercar, steering like Schumacher
コパイロットはチューバッカ 次限が違う連中ばっか
Co-pilot is Chewbacca, just a bunch of folks from a different dimension
Ayy, コーナー攻めてギリギリ
Ayy, cornering on the edge
モーター全開 地響き
Motor full throttle, sounding like an earthquake
空から導き
Guided from the sky
お肌がピチピチ
Skin is glowing
タイヤ焦がして ドーナツターン
Burning tires, donut turn
弾け飛んでいく ドラム缶
Drum cans flying off
顧客満足度 高くて
High customer satisfaction
ぶち上がってる お客さん
Clients are pumped
0から最高到達点
From 0 to the highest point
溜めてる太陽光発電
Storing up solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒 突入ボーナスデー
Super awakening, entering bonus day
一直線 伸びてる道路
Straight road extending
バイブレーション エンジンの稼働
Vibration engine in operation
速度増し上がってる鼓動
Increasing speed, heartbeat
限界重力 凌駕上昇
Surpassing limit gravity, rising
開拓しまくってく フロンティア
Pioneering the frontier
旅立つなら明日 オンリーワン
If you set off, tomorrow, only one
アクセル踏み込んでく ドンピシャ
Stepping on the gas, perfectly
飛んでいく日本いざ
Flying off, Japan now
1億馬力の重低音
100 million horsepower heavy bass
火星の果てまで 休憩中
Resting until the ends of Mars
並んで走行 UFO
Flying side-by-side with a UFO
降り立つ 宇宙ステーション
Landing on the space station
物語を継承
Inheriting the story
まるで空飛ぶ聖書
Just like a flying bible
この先の世紀も成長
Growing through the coming centuries
生き延びて Get a Daystar
Surviving, get a Daystar
叶うはずはマスター
Destined to come true, Master
心臓がモンスター
Heart is a monster
エリアはサタミナ
Area is Saturn
FG パーティーは
FG Party is...
光るテスラ・ロッサ
Shining Testarossa
ヘビーブースター 目覚めていく本能
Heavy booster, awakening instinct
蒼い炎
Blue flame
V-I-P Let's go out
So get in the car
0から宇宙まで とらわれず走る
Run from 0 to space, without being trapped
FG ROADSTER 唸るブースター
FG ROADSTER, roaring booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 Chase me!
Now, chase me!
...the place to be
今 チェイスミー
Now, chase me
以上、私たち Flow Glow でした！
That was us, Flow Glow!
こっから先も 楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep having fun from here on!
Tame the fire, and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm Infamous,
yeah, I get a little villainous.
Look into my eyes I'll seek you out
Reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by chains, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my maze feel my pulse is rising
and igniting fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line on the edge of
Becoming what I never thought I'd be better
This stand or gonna take them all out
Renegade!
Walking the line fell so far
Into poison and I see me a new-gotcha
Locked and loaded take them all out
Renegade! Justice is just like that
I don't care at all, I'll go deeper till I can't quit
Never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little bit
The lights go out!
Make 'em fall down, make 'em, make 'em last, switch
Make 'em, make 'em fall down and they crash
Renegade!
Make 'em fall down, make 'em, make 'em last, switch
Make 'em, make 'em fall down and they crash
Renegade!
Bound by power, pretty one desiring
Never making sounds, in the middle of all the battle
Burning a mountain, follow us in the ashes
Yeah, snuff it out
Walking the line on the edge of
Becoming what I never thought I'd be better
This stand or gonna take them all out
Renegade!
Walking the line fell so far
Into poison and I see me a new-gotcha
Locked and loaded take them all out
Renegade! Justice is just like that
I don't care at all, I'll go deeper till I can't quit
Never gonna stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little bit
The lights go out!
Tame the fire, and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm Infamous,
yeah, I get a little villainous.
The lights go out!
空覚えだらけの人生ゲーム
A life game full of rote learning
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following a heart full of excuses
現実はハンザカラーフロートです
Reality is a Hansa-color float
取り憑かれるオーバーな衝動
Possessed by an over-the-top impulse
言い足りずなあの娘はね
That girl who doesn't say enough...
二度被った猫はずさない
She won't take off her cat suit
一目惚れしてしまったマジシャン
The magician I fell for at first sight
手の内はまだ明かせない
Still can't reveal the hand
Yellow, yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow, yellow, a loop from zero
点滅するピリオド
A flashing period
And what if I can make or not?
たとえ 月に見放されても
Even if I'm forsaken by the moon...
No worries 私には私が付いてる
No worries, I've got myself by my side
酔いが醒めるまで あと少しだけ
Until I sober up, just a little longer
真実を捉える残像 So let's win the race
The afterimage capturing truth, so let's win the race
次の季節を越え Bloom me Bloom me
Beyond the next season, Bloom me, Bloom me
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound
Our Time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow ずっと最高
Our Time Yellow, Yellow, let it flow, let it flow, always the best
Our Time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow Oh oh
Let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror 絡まってる蜘蛛の糸
Look into the mirror, the tangled spider webs
It happens all time 躍らされた独り言
It happens all the time, dancing soliloquies
正気について時を編んで明け暮れて
Spending days and nights weaving time with sanity
Always be honest 永遠に変わらないもの
Always be honest, things that never change
Yellow Yellow 手を取り合えば そこに理由はいらない
Yellow, Yellow, if we hold hands, we need no reason
Yellow Yellow 染まる赤い結晶 甘い症状 Bad bad
Yellow, Yellow, red crystals staining, sweet symptoms, bad bad
一挙手一投足 希望に等しいデスロール 過ぎた運命や人生ごと受け入れ
Every move, a death roll like hope; accepting past fate and life
信じ手に取って 4. 3. 2. 1. Jump around Step by step
Believe and take it, 4-3-2-1, jump around, step by step
走り抜ける ゼン・オア・セブン 終着地点はエデン・オア・ヘブン
Running through, then or seven, the destination is Eden or Heaven
No time to waste 今だけを信じて 最後のフィナーレまで共に進め
No time to waste, believe only in the now, let's move together to the finale
酔いが醒めるまで あと少しだけ
Until I sober up, just a little longer
真実を捉える残像 So let's win the race
The afterimage capturing truth, so let's win the race
次の季節を越え Bloom me Bloom me
Beyond the next season, Bloom me, Bloom me
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please, don't stop this sound
Our Time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow ずっと最高
Our Time Yellow, Yellow, let it flow, let it flow, always the best
Our Time Yellow Yellow Let it flow Let it flow Oh oh
Let's enjoy the moment
またねー！
See ya!
See you!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
This is where my story all begins!
Livin' on the edge of crazy
Waitin' for the break of day now
Throw it away so easy
I can't get enough
Raise the bar, no limit
Haven't you heard of me, feelings?
Give and go, let's do this
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me...
Watch me, watch me, be your diva
I'm gonna raise your fever
Shakin' up all the crowd
Makin' some noise when I'm not allowed
Livin' my life out loud
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding
I keep indulging in my anthem
Oh, oh, oh, don't blame me, the way I shine so bright
Oh, oh, oh, can't help it if I start a fire
Oh, oh, oh, pay attention
Cause this is only the beginning... It's our genesis!
Come and wreak some havoc
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness
(Can you hear it?)
Whispers banging down your window (Oh, yeah, oh, yeah)
Rumors reaching a crescendo (Ah-ha-ha)
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, woah-oh
Midnight, diamonds in the dark side (Oh, yeah, oh, yeah)
Stay right, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
And mayhem in action
I know what day it is, this is our genesis!
Oh, entering the rave when I misbehave, take center stage
Oh, with the fun commands but you know I'm gonna get in check
There are loopholes unspoken, the rules can all be broken
I'm running on a rampage, the world is a blank page
Let's go, I'm writing my story in flames and in glory
Cause they're gonna know me by name by now
Oh, oh, oh, and this is my promised land
Oh, oh, oh, the future's in my hands
Oh, oh, oh, today I understand
That I'm a star in the making, awaking, awaking, awaking!
Pow, pow, pow, pow
Tell me how you like me now
Let's celebrate the New Year!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your voice go and let me show you how to lose control
You've got the freedom on your mind, keep your eyes on me behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings
A death-defying, world-shaking
I'm sure you've heard of me by now
Midnight, join me to the light side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My rhyme is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our Genesis
Tell me what time it is
IT'S OUR GENESIS!
君に届けたい
I want to deliver this to you
Id:entity
id:entity voices
ステージに一歩を踏み出した
Taking the first step onto the stage
(おはよう こんばんは) と世界に叫んでみよう
(Good morning! Good evening!) Let's shout out to the world
本日のライブでは どれの自分を見せるの？
In today's live, which 'me' will I show?
前からそう悩んで 好きな自分になれない
I've been worried about this for a long time, I can't become the 'me' I want to be
そしである日誰かに言われた
And then, one day, someone told me
偉大な言葉なんてに迷っていた いつも
I was lost in the words, always
とびきりの笑顔を失わないように
Keep your smile, don't lose it
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided I won't betray this expectation anymore
溢れている 雑音の中
Overflowing in the noise
この声響けるか？
Can you hear this voice?
心に宿る 声を聞いてみよう
Let's try listening to the voice that dwells in the heart
これはずっと見せたい自分だった
This is the 'me' I always wanted to show
集まった声たちがひとつになる
The collected voices become one
id:entity voices.
月日が過ぎてやっとスポットライトに
Time has passed, and finally in the spotlight
立てるけれど少しだけ怖くなった
I can stand here, but I've become a little afraid
でもね一人じゃない 仲間たちがいるんだ
But you know, I'm not alone, my friends are here
家族みたいな絆で 違いが分かり合えた
With a bond like family, we understood our differences
それぞれも 輝き合って
Each of us shining together
ハーモニー奏でるかな
I wonder if we'll create harmony
手を繋いで 共に夢の空の方へ
Holding hands, together towards the sky of dreams
精一杯 歓声を上げましょう
Let's raise our cheers with all our might
幸せを届けるんだ どこにだって 響けよ
We're delivering happiness, let it ring out everywhere
新しい舞台に飛び込んで 今...
Diving into a new stage, now...
鳴らす音色を
The sounds we ring out,
止めないでいて
please don't let them stop.
ここに集めたこの音色が
These sounds gathered here...
震えるハーモニーになって
become a trembling harmony.
心の迷いが消えていく
The hesitation in my heart fades away.
これからずっとこの自分のままで
Staying as my true self from now on.
集まった声たちが
Even if the voices that have gathered...
違っても揺るがないと信じて
are different, I believe they won't waver.
一つになるアイデンティティ
Becoming one, Identity.
Selamat pagi semua!
Good morning, everyone!
お疲れ様でした！
Thank you for your hard work!
Selamat malam semua!
Good evening, everyone!
また会う日まで
Until the day we meet again.
我ら エデンの星を統べる者 秘密結社holoX！
We are the rulers of the Star of Eden, Secret Society holoX!
holoX、見参でござる！
holoX, appearing!
機は熟した 2026年を待つ貴様ら！
The time is ripe! You lots waiting for 2026!
暁闇エクスデス
Gyouan Death
準備はいいか？
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
The night deepens, look, Darkness.
ノワール 誰だかは凡で隠す
Noir, hiding who I am with mediocrity.
縄に従え どいつも Instinct
Obey the rope, everyone's Instinct.
まことにお耳侍る
Verily, I attend to your ears.
病みつきじゃないけど ルーペでどうでしょう チェケチェケ
It's not an addiction, but how about a loupe? Check it.
センスであればOK 君抱くあかさたな ジャジャジャ
If you have sense, it's OK; the alphabet you hold, Ja Ja Ja.
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
In the palm of evil, you'll want to dance.
ほら君も 気付けばノリノリで
See, even you are grooving before you know it.
どうしようもない どうしようもない 堕ちていく運命
Helpless, helpless, the fate of falling down.
難所じゃない 混ぜる全部塗り替えよう
It's not a difficult spot; let's mix and repaint it all.
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Where X, X, X, and X intersect in the middle,
NextとNextとNextへ 運命はもう 始まってる
to Next, Next, and Next; fate has already begun.
暁闇のエクスデス
Gyouan Death.
混沌としたこの世界を 我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
This chaotic world, we shall repaint it in holoX colors!
皆の者 続け！
Everyone, follow me!
Yes my Dark!
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
La+殿と世界征服！
World domination with La+!
Madam Hawk Eye!
はい 今見てる皆様は もうホロクサーですよ
Yes, everyone watching now is already a holoXer.
こよりにうむ配合！
Mixing Koyorinium!
2026年も ずっと一緒だよ
We'll be together throughout 2026 too.
風先まで 鏡開き！
To the tip of the wind, kagami-biraki!
一刀両断 叩き切れ！
Cut them down with a single stroke!
どうしようもない どうしようもない 堕ちていく運命
Helpless, helpless, the fate of falling down.
難所じゃない 混ぜる全部塗り替えよう
It's not a difficult spot; let's mix and repaint it all.
刮目せよ！
Witness!
XとXとXとXが 交差する真ん中で
Where X, X, X, and X intersect in the middle,
NextとNextとNextへ 運命はもう 始まってる
to Next, Next, and Next; fate has already begun.
ホロクステ
holoX-te
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight,
Down in the streetlights,
Looking for a spotlight,
Making my move.
(Whoa)
I'm running.
行こう！
Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind don't stop coming,
Got me in a tailspin, what can I do?
(Whoa)
Keep running!
行こう!!
Let's go!!
Lost and found, back to where I started.
I won't stay down, trust me, I can do it.
I live life loud, take it to the limit.
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it.
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning.
Run back 'round, got to keep believing.
Run back 'round, I know where I'm going.
Run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now.
(Whoa)
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on paper,
Dreams in the distance,
Got to be relentless,
Faster than sound.
(Whoa)
Keep running!
行こう！
Let's go!
Locked and loaded, 僕らは explosive
Locked and loaded, we are explosive
Swifter and lighter, 明日はきっと brighter
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow's surely brighter
Faster than lightning, また冒険 exciting
Faster than lightning, another exciting adventure
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning.
Run back 'round, got to keep believing.
Run back 'round, I know where I'm going.
Run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now.
(Whoa)
I'm gonna run back 'round!
走って 走って 走って
Running, running, running,
I'm gonna run back 'round!
始まるよ 変わるよ
It's beginning, it's changing,
Look at the dreams just waiting,
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Everybody!
Everybody come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Hololive! You guys ready?
To greet the New Year? Hell yeah!
No time to waste!
Let's get it started!
誕生のフレアを 巻き散らして
Scattering the flare of birth,
困難だらけの人生だけど
life is full of difficulties, but...
縦横無尽にスラップして 楽しんじゃおう
let's slap all over the place and have fun!
Fly like a feather, sorry! 立ち塞がる壁なんて
Fly like a feather, sorry! Whatever walls stand...
さぁ 越えて行こう
in our way, come on, let's go over them!
Fly like a feather, sorry! 止まれないんじゃなくて
Fly like a feather, sorry! It's not that I can't stop,
止まらないんだ
I just won't stop!
Step by stepで空中散歩 私なりで
Walking in the air step by step, in my own way.
隙あらばその瞬間 歓声 沼にハマっちゃおう
If there's an opening, at that moment, let's...
沼にハマっちゃおう
get stuck in the cheers and the swamp.
1, 2, 3で真相心理 クラッシュして
Crash the deep-seated psychology with 1, 2, 3!
止まらない現実を更新 ハードモードなライフを
Updating the reality that won't stop, a...
塗りつぶしていけ
hard-mode life, paint it over!
仰ぐ最色のダンスフロア
Looking up at the most colorful dance floor
どんなウェイな平手打ちも
Any kind of 'way' slap
キャラも外さないで
Don't lose your character
見合わしたコンボスプラッシュ
A matching combo splash
Clap your hands and stand up please
飛び込んじゃっても なせば成る それがセオリーさ
Even if you dive in, you can do it—that's the theory
Clap your hands and stand up please
事態後悔を ステップに変えりゃ最高っしょ
Changing regret into steps is the best, right?
違っても同じ想い
Even if we're different, we have the same feelings
だから、ここから
So, from here...
Slap by stepで行こうぜ
Let's go slap by step
360度私なりで
360 degrees in my own way
隙あらばその瞬間に
Whenever there's a chance, in that moment
完全に掌握 沼にハマっちゃえ
Complete control—fall into the swamp!
1 2 3 で真相心理
With a 1, 2, 3, deep inside the heart...
クラッシュして
...it crashes
今すぐで 私たちの色に
Right now, dyed in our colors
染めあげた 世界を見せる
We'll show you the world we've dyed
皆様、今年の応援ありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you for your support this year!
ホロIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ、ずっと見ててね！
HoloID will get even more exciting, keep watching!
来年もよろしくお願いします！ See you next year!
Please support us next year too! See you next year!
ウンッ！皆様、森カリオペです！
Umm! Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up, hololive English -Myth- coming right at ya for a brand new year!
今年すごい盛り上がったね！来年もよろしく！
It was so exciting this year! Let's do it next year too!
We're gonna rock the world ten times harder next year. You in? Next up, Ina!
Wah! Hello everyone, this is Ina! Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年すごく楽しかったです！来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
This year was so much fun! Please look forward to next year too!
Yeah, let's go! Next is Kiwawa!
キキキ！小鳥遊キアラです！
Kiki! I'm Takanashi Kiara!
キアラらしく盛り上げるぞー！
I'll liven things up in Kiara style!
ギャー！ Myth is here!
Gya! Myth is here!
Let's have fun in 2026 too!
Let's go! やりましょうか！
Let's go! Shall we do it?
2026年もよろしく！
Please look forward to 2026 too!
Alright, let's show them what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper truth or dare
A hand's a thread led to the world
But no one's keeping score
Set a course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down but I'm a winner
I play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A future in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread
I see what's up ahead
A wild chase, a perfect face
I've got to try my luck and spin the wheel
Spin the roulette see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and round jumping into the circle
Over and over a test of will
Though the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates we're betting on
Their heart unbroken
Called to life by flex and string
Casting lots together
At the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet
It spins back around with every chance I get
Under this tangled thread
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red
I'm moving up ahead
A perfect chance and a starry dance
I spin this thread, the fate's with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
After this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び出そう
Let's jump out
Come on baby
輝いて
Shine bright
ハートきゅんって
My heart is fluttering
Pump It up
Hyper Jumpin'
夢の先まで
Beyond the dreams
もっと もっと
More and more
刺激が欲しいの
I want more stimulation
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'!
子供みたいにはしゃぐ方が お得でしょ
It's better to frolic like a child, right?
テイクオフから 這い上がっていくテンション
Tension rising up from takeoff
宵長 打ち返し捲るメンション
Hitting back mentions repeatedly through the long night
カウントを乗りこなして進むミッション
Mission progressing while riding the count
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating the speed just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Feelings that won't stop are gaining momentum
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ！
Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
跳び跳ねよう
Let's jump around
ハイになって 肺になるまで
Becoming high until I turn to ashes
Don't stop, 止まんな！
Don't stop, don't stop!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' beyond the sky
もっと もっと
More and more
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Woah woah woah
ドキドキしたい Give me, give me, give me eyes
I want to feel my heart pounding, give me eyes
Woah woah woah
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
More and more, I want to jump higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'!
斜めから 攻めていけ スクエション
Attack from an angle, equation
ネガティブを 切り裂いていく 天上
Tearing through the negative, heavens
流れるコメントと かけあい セッション
Session interacting with flowing comments
エイムを鍛えて 狙いうつ プレッシャー
Pressure aiming while training the aim
Freeze one no no
不意打ちなら mama mama
If it's a surprise attack, mama mama
邪魔するノイズは 吹き消せ bang bang bang
Blow away the distracting noise, bang bang bang
遊んでいたいだけ 味わい尽くして
I just want to play, enjoying it to the fullest
笑い飛ばして
Laugh it off
蹴っ飛ばして
Kick it away
キッキング
Kicking
Japan Japan
このまま僕らは旅をして
We continue our journey just like this
辿り着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what lies at the destination
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こう
Let's go beyond dimensions
さあ！
Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper Jumpin' let's leap over
ハイになって 肺になるまで
Becoming high until I turn to ashes
Don't stop, 止まんな！
Don't stop, don't stop!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper Jumpin' beyond the sea
もっと もっと
More and more
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
Woah woah woah
ドキドキしたい Give me, give me, give me eyes
I want to feel my heart pounding, give me eyes
Woah woah woah
もっと もっと 高く跳びたいの
More and more, I want to jump higher
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
目を開け
Open your eyes
目を覚まして
Wake yourself up
夢から抜け出して
Escape from the dream
世界が今、目撃する
The world now witnesses
我らの蘇り
Our resurrection
鏡に映る
Reflecting in the mirror
心に宿っている
That dwells in the heart
小さいヒカリ
A small light
そう、今も感じる
Yes, I still feel it
何処かこの奥で
Somewhere deep inside
呼び覚ました
Awakened
忘れられない
Unforgettable
浮かぶメモリー
Floating memories
今の自分になる
Before becoming the self...
その前に
...I am now
果てのない
Lost in an endless
迷路で迷い
maze
そして黄昏が
And the twilight
落ちてくる
is falling
何処までも
Everywhere
引き締める
The chain that tightens
クサリが鳴らす
is ringing
体温を止めてた
Stopping the body temperature
ためらいを
Hesitation
覚えてしまって
I've learned it
凍えていくの
and I'm freezing
足の向こう側に
Beyond the feet
道なるエリア
an unknown area
その境界線の
Beyond that boundary line
先に待つのは
is waiting
15の始め
The beginning of 15
目覚めは変わらず
The awakening is unchanged
奈落の底へと
To the bottom of the abyss
落ちていく
Falling
時間さえ知らぬ
Even time unknown
時計の針の音
The sound of the clock hands
手掛かりなく
With no clue
記憶に残り
Remaining in memory
広がる海
The spreading sea
どこまでも知らない
Anywhere unknown
森の中に
In the forest
宇宙を超え
Beyond the universe
逃げ場所探して
Searching for a place to escape
そんな過去もまだ
Such a past is still
頭に響いている
Echoing in my head
ほどけないクサリを断ち
Break the chains that won't come loose
切れないままもがき
Struggling while unable to cut them
物語の始まり
The beginning of the story
探し続けたい
I want to keep searching
未詳で不確かな
Unknown and uncertain
謎のようなことさ
Like a mystery
この身体の中で目覚めた
Awakened inside this body
本当の姿
My true form
運命のカードが占う未来
The future predicted by the cards of fate
深層へ
To the depths...
お前を
I won't
離さない
let you go
解き放ったクサリが消え
The released chains disappear
進めると信じて
Believing that I can move forward
新たな自分になって
Becoming a new self
光の方へ
Towards the light
ついに辿り着いた
Finally reached
未知なるエリア
An unknown area
その境界線を超える日が来た
The day to cross that boundary line has come
15の果て
The end of 15
XV-iltration
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in each other
挑戦の狼煙をあげよう
Let's raise the signal fire of challenge
終わらない
To an endless
青春に
Youth
Woah-woah-woah-oh-oh
Boys and girls 羞恥心は捨てて Hey, jump!
Boys and girls, throw away your shame, Hey, jump!
みんなで揃えば Cool jump! Jump!
If we all gather together, Cool jump! Jump!
信じ合う仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in each other,
挑戦の狼煙をあげよう
let's raise the smoke of a challenge.
終わらない 青春に
To the endless youth.
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show how I've grown.
リハーサル完璧 本番はもっと全力で
Rehearsal was perfect, the real show will be even more full power!
大切な思い出
Precious memories,
たくさんあるけど まだ
there are many, but still...
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental.
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century begins.
想像の果てにある高み
The height beyond imagination,
勝ち取った景色は尊い
the scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits.
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
冷たい豪雨に溺れたって
Even if we drown in cold heavy rain,
確かな希望をたぐり寄せるように
as if to pull in a certain hope.
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it's disappointing.
痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
Pain and pain always fight each other.
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting relying only on pride.
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to be sentimental.
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century begins.
反響が足りない もっともっと
Not enough echo, more and more!
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it.
想像の果てにある高み
The height beyond imagination,
勝ち取った景色は尊い
the scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな限界の壁越えて
Don't run away, cross the wall of limits.
僕らはまだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
重ねた手はギュッと
Our overlapping hands, tightly...
離さずに
never letting go.
行くよ！（行こう！）
Let's go! (Let's go!)
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky.
窓越しに見上げた
I looked up through the window...
とても小さな空
at the very small sky.
ここで出会えたのは
What I met here is...
数え切れないキセキ
countless miracles.
繰り返した一歩が
Every repeated step...
キラメキをつないで
connects the sparkle.
星のような笑顔 導いた
Guided by a star-like smile,
day by day
みんなの声がチカラになる
Everyone's voice becomes my strength,
stage by stage
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
Here, what each of us aims for,
それぞれ描くもの
what each of us draws,
それぞれ願った夢へ
to the dream each of us wished for.
重ねた手はギュッと 離さずに
Overlapping hands tightly, without letting go.
一人一人違う色で
Each one with a different color,
描き出す ときめき
drawing out the excitement.
振り向くことなく 真っ直ぐに
Without looking back, straight ahead.
行くよ！（行こう！）
Let's go! (Let's go!)
夢見る空へ
To the dreaming sky.
笑い合ったことや
The times we laughed together,
尽きない我が儘
and endless selfishness.
思い出いっぱいなのに
Even though it's full of memories...
あっという間の日々
In the blink of an eye, these days...
上書きじゃなくって 名前つけて保存
Are saved not by overwriting, but as new files
どれも全部大事って
That every single one is precious
言い切れる
I can say for sure
One for all
みんなの糧が力になる
Everyone's support becomes our strength
All for one
ちょっと賑やかすぎるくらい
Even if it's a bit too noisy
笑顔がもう止まらない
The smiles just won't stop
思いは膨らんでいく
Our feelings keep swelling up
重ねた今 ギュッと
Holding this moment tightly
噛み締めた
I savor it
一人一人違う声で
With each of our different voices
歌えばほら広がる
Look, as we sing, it spreads out
風を感じたら
When we feel the breeze
まっすぐに
We'll head straight
行くよ！ 行こうよ！ 夢見る空へ
Let's go! Let's go! Towards the sky of our dreams
憧れ 手を伸ばし
Reaching out towards what I long for
掴み取った その光が
The light that I finally grasped
いつの日か
One day...
また誰かの憧れに変わる
It will become someone else's dream
つなげよう
Let's pass it on
重ねた手はギュッと 離さずに
Holding hands tightly, don't let go
一人一人違う色で
With each of our different colors
描き出すトキメキ
Drawing out this excitement
出会ったすべてに ありがとう
Thank you for everything we've encountered
奇跡だって起こし続け
Continuing to make miracles happen
ずっと ずっと そばにいるよ
I'll be by your side forever and ever
行くよ！ 行こうよ！
Let's go! Let's go!
夢見る空へ
Towards the sky of our dreams
ホロライブゲーマーズ！
Hololive Gamers!
フブキだよー！
It's Fubuki!
ミオだよー！
It's Mio!
おかゆだよー！
It's Okayu!
ころねだよー！
It's Korone!
We are GAMERS!!!!
コン狐きつねが 登場
The corn-fox makes her entrance
白上狐 白上フブキで
White fox, Shirakami Fubuki
突っ込んじゃ始まらない
It won't start if you keep quibbling
君はすこん部に入部しなさい
You must join the Sukon-bu
はい！
Yes!
イェーイ！
Yay!
コンコンと絶好調 頂戴
In top form, give me a "Kon-Kon"
エアじゃないし得意はMC
It's not just talk, MCing is my specialty
あざといよりキレとかが美味しい
Sharpness is better than being "calculated"
ミオだよー！
It's Mio!
ウチウチウチだよ 大神ミオだよ
It's me, me, me! It's Ookami Mio!
黒髪ケモ耳 狼
Black hair, fluffy ears, a wolf
突っ込んで止めます 雷お母様
The lightning mom will put a stop to it
笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
Once she starts laughing, she can't stop
妻に実はポエムを どう？
Actually, how about a poem for my wife?
腰ステップしちゃおっと
I'll do a hip step
タロット占いで見る未来
Seeing the future with tarot readings
ほら ゲームはやりたくない！
Look, I don't want to play horror games!
4人で集まれば GAMERS ultimate
The four of us together are GAMERS ultimate
参加して Bダッシュ
Join in and B-dash
レベル上げで目指せクリア
Level up and aim for the clear
今日は何を遊ぶ？
What shall we play today?
君のハートも コーデしちゃう
I'll coordinate your heart too
選択をしてシミュレーション
Make your choice and simulate
初見も古参も 大丈夫
Whether it's your first time or you're a vet
さあ ゲームは楽しいね
Come on, games are fun, right?
G A M E R S
We are GAMERS!!!!
おかゆ！
Okayu!
いくよ もぐもぐ 猫又おかゆ
Here we go, munch munch, Nekomata Okayu
おにぎり おにぎり はいどうぞ
Rice ball, rice ball, here you go
キラキラ ふらふら 宵の猫だもん
Twinkling and wobbling, I'm a night cat
ほーら 僕でよくない？
Look, aren't I good enough?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
A chill, slow, bouncing rhythm
全肯定する おかゆイズム
The "Okayu-ism" of total affirmation
全肯定降臨 おっけー！
Total affirmation descends, okay!
毎日僕と一緒に
With me every day
ころね！
Korone!
オハヨ！ 指指 ワーワー
Mornin'! Fingers, fingers, wa-wa!
パンはこれこれ 犬神ころね
The bread's gotta be this, Inugami Korone
キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Cavalier King Charles Spaniel
パピヨン 豆柴 アフガンハウンド
Papillon, Mameshiba, Afghan Hound
なまるイントネーション 割れるリアクション
A dialectal intonation and big reactions
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ はい、視聴！
First, will you offer your fingers? Yes, viewer!
わかったなら返事して オッケー
If you understand, reply with an "okay"
好物のレタコロッケ お届け
Delivering my favorite lettuce croquettes
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are gamers
狐らしく現る狐　艶やかな白い髪とケモ耳
A fox appearing just like a fox,
with lustrous white hair and furry ears
守護る狼　絆を探して
A guardian wolf, searching for bonds
気まぐれ猫　一言でハートを盗む
A whimsical cat, stealing hearts with just a word
尻尾振る犬　どこまでも追いかけるよ
A tail-wagging dog, I'll chase you anywhere
4人で　We are the GAMERS ultimate
Together, the four of us are the GAMERS ultimate
ジョインして　Bダッシュで
Join us, with a B-dash
レベルアップして　クリア目指そう
Level up and aim to clear
今日は何プレイしようか？
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
I'll restore your heart
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です！
Suddenly, it's time for a bonus challenge!
大きな声でレスポンスして、高得点を狙いましょう！
Let's aim for a high score by responding loudly!
Are you ready?
せーの！コンコン！
One, two! Kon-kon!
せーの！みょんみょん！
One, two! Myon-myon!
せーの！もぐもぐ！
One, two! Mogu-mogu!
せーの！ゆびゆび！
One, two! Yubi-yubi!
せーの！コンコン！
One, two! Kon-kon!
せーの！みょんみょん！
One, two! Myon-myon!
せーの！もぐもぐ！
One, two! Mogu-mogu!
せーの！ゆびゆび！
One, two! Yubi-yubi!
完璧！
Perfect!
狐らしく現る狐　目指せ最強
A fox appearing just like a fox, aiming for the top
うまくいかなくてもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, continue
低速リスナーまであきらめない
Never giving up, even for slow listeners
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending
君のハートを攻略しちゃう
I'll conquer your heart
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices and simulating
初見さんも古参さんも代わる代わる
First-timers and veterans alike, taking turns
やっぱゲームは楽しいね！
Games are fun after all!
We are GAMERS!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった...
And so, the curtain closed on the year 2025...
生まれたてのドキドキを　響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heart-pounding resound
最高の時間
The best time
最高の仲間と
With the best companions
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
イェーイ！
Yeah!
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider
覚えてるかな？　最初の歌
Do you remember? Our very first song
懐かしいね
It's nostalgic
私　声が震えていた
My voice was trembling
ほんの少し
Just a little bit
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continues from that day
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
Is the today we grasped together
もっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more
加速するハート
Our hearts are accelerating
一緒に行こうよ　どこまでも
Let's go together, anywhere
I'm ready?
準備はOK？
Are you ready?
開け　夢の扉を
Open the door to dreams
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
生まれたてのドキドキを　響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heart-pounding resound
最高の時間　最高の仲間と
The best time, with the best companions
ここにいるよ　見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to see you
みんなで歌おう
Let's all sing together
終わらないメロディー
The melody that never ends
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle
届いてるかな？　私の声
Is my voice reaching you?
はっきりと
Clearly
届けたいのは　君に笑顔
What I want to deliver is a smile to you
そのスマイル
That smile
理想の交差に悔しくて
Frustrated at the intersection of ideals
みんなと泣き笑ったね
We cried and laughed together
ギュッとギュッとギュッとギュッと
Tight, tight, tight, tight
すべて抱きしめて
Embracing it all
一緒に行こう　どこまでも
Let's go together, anywhere
I'm ready?
準備はOK？
Are you ready?
進め　自分の道を
Go forward on your own path
1, 2, 3! キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3! Kirameki Rider
好きな気持ちカラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my feelings colorfully
最高の場所　最高のみんなと
The best place, with everyone
ここにいるよ　幻なんかじゃない
I'm here, it's no illusion
君の心が幸せに染まるように
So that your heart may be dyed in happiness
重ねていくハーモニー
The harmony we layer together
キラメキ纏って
Clad in sparkle
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing
そんな願いやわがままもいいでしょ？
Wishes and selfishness like those are okay, right?
だって楽しすぎて
Because it's just too much fun
もう止まらない
I can't stop anymore
輝くステージでもっともっと
On the shining stage, even more, even more...
ずっと！
Forever!
嬉しい 楽しい 愛おしいだけじゃ語れない
Joy, fun, and love alone aren't enough to describe it
今も今も悩みはあるけど
Even now, there are still worries, but...
ここにいるよ
I'm right here
私 ここにいるよ
I am right here
君と同じ世界を見つめて
Gazing at the same world as you
キラメキライダー☆
Kirameki Rider☆
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's make the fresh excitement resonate
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time and the best friends
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here because you found me
私のために日々日々お仕事励んでくれてありがとう
Thank you for working hard every day for my sake
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 お願いね！
Definitely, definitely, definitely... Please!
この この この... うー この この この... この この この...
Kono, kono, kono... Whoo! Kono, kono, kono...
銀河の果てまで推してほしい
I want you to support me to the ends of the galaxy!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grab that dream
それぞれ
Each of us
違った
With different
心で
Hearts
走れ
Let's run!
どこを見ても真っ暗な
Everywhere I look, it's pitch black
場所に芽生えてた
Sprouting in such a place
ほんの小さな希望に
By a tiny sliver of hope
この瞳奪われた
My eyes were captivated
不安に揺れる心を
My heart, wavering in anxiety
上手くチューニングして
I tuned it just right
ほんの小さな勇気を
Summoning every bit...
振り絞っていたんだよ
...of my tiny courage
諦めの文字で
With the word 'give up'
デリートして進む
Deleted, I move forward
もしも辛い時も
Even if there are tough times
もう私は
I'm already
一人じゃないから
Not alone anymore
だからもっと夢を追いかけたい
So I want to chase my dreams even more
ワクワク止まらない
I can't stop the excitement
想像を越えてく
Going beyond imagination
世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world
アクセルふかしてみて
Try stepping on the gas
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you have any regrets
それぞれ違った
Each of us with different
心で
Hearts
走れ
Let's run!
嘘の空に輝く
Shining in the false sky
眩しい想いは
Dazzling feelings
見たこともない光も
Even light I've never seen
リアルに届けるよ
I'll deliver them for real
いつも聞こえるエールを
Always hearing the cheers
ここにキャプチャーして
Capturing them here
また新しい光を
Once again, a new light...
探したくなるよ
...I'll want to go search for
君の笑顔は
Your smile
ほどよくて進む
Keeps me going along
悲しい時に
In sad times
見返すよ
I'll look back at it
ちからがわくから
Because it gives me strength
胸を張って夢を追いかけたい
With my chest high, I want to chase my dreams
軌跡のストーリー
A story of tracks
一緒に作ろう
Let's make it together
終わらない夢を
A never-ending dream
誰一人欠かせない
No one is left behind
アイを待つこの世界
This world waiting for love
それぞれ違った
Each of us with different
心で
Hearts
彩れ
Color it!
苦しい時も
Even in painful times
寂しい時も
Even in lonely times
信じ合えるものがあるはずなのに
Even though there should be things to believe in...
この鼓動
This heartbeat...
鳴らし続けたい
...I want to keep it ringing
広がる世界に溢れ出すよ
It'll overflow into the expanding world
笑顔たち
All those smiles
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on that stage I admire
眩しく輝きたい
I want to shine dazzlingly
時には涙して
Sometimes shedding tears
また笑い合いたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手にしたい
I want to grab that dream
踏み出そう
Let's step forward
奇跡の一歩を
Miraculous first step
息切らして夢を追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to chase my dreams
ワクワク止まらない
I can't stop the excitement
想像を越えてく
Going beyond imagination
世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world
アクセスしてみてよ
Try accessing it
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here
それぞれ違った
Each of us with different
心で
Hearts
作るんだ
We'll create it!
みんな、コークは持ったかな？
Everyone, do you have your Coke?
ポチりました！乾杯するー！
I ordered mine! Let's toast!
こらこら、早いよラプちゃん。
Hey, hey, you're too early, La-chan.
避けるな！当たる！
Don't dodge! It'll hit!
年越しのタイミングで、みんなで乾杯ってするんだよ。
We're supposed to toast together at the turn of the year.
やだやだもう喉カラカラ！
No way, I'm already thirsty!
楽しみだね。ね、みこさん？みこさん？
I'm looking forward to it. Right, Miko-san? Miko-san?
ライブだったね。
That was quite a live performance.
お疲れー！
Good work!
この後どうする？ご飯食べる？
What should we do after this? Grab some food?
いや、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Well, won't everywhere be crowded?
確かに。お腹空きましたね。
True. I'm hungry.
あ、運転手さん、真っ直ぐね。
Oh, driver, go straight.
お前ら！何帰ってんだ！
You guys! Why are you going home?!
乾杯、乾杯！
Toast, toast!
フブちゃんたちがついてきてる。
Fubu-chan and the others are following us.
おらおら、フブスワン寂しくなっちゃったのかね？
Hey, hey, did Fubuswan get lonely?
なんか怒ってない？
Don't they look angry?
おえ？あ、やばい。あのイタズラがバレたかな？
Eh? Oh no. Did that prank get found out?
やりすぎだったかな？
Did we go too far?
やばいかも。運転手さん、ごめん！
This might be bad. Driver, sorry!
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞ！
I'll escape with Miko's driving skills!
あ、来た！
Oh, they're here!
すごいすごい！
Amazing, amazing!
フブちゃんごめんて、もうイタズラしないから！
Fubu-chan, sorry! We won't prank you anymore!
だめだよみこみこ、反省しなさい。
No, Miko-miko, reflect on what you did.
お前も共犯だろうが！
You were an accomplice too!
何の話だ。
What are you talking about?
二人ともこれ持って。
Both of you, take these.
何するの？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ。
It's almost the New Year.
10, 9, 8, 7
6, 5, 4, 3
2, 1!
乾杯！！
Toast!!
明けましておめでとう！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくね。
Looking forward to another great year.
お腹いっぱーい。
I'm full!
そういえば、イタズラって何なの？
By the way, what was that prank?
あ、それね。フブさんのへそ増やしたんだよ。
Oh, that. I added more navels to Fubu-san.
恐怖！
Terror!
この後は、コカ・コーラと一緒に、スペシャルライブステージ！
And next, a special live stage with Coca-Cola!
SPECIAL STAGE
そうさ ずっと僕らの奇跡が
Yes, let's sing so our miracle...
途切れないように歌うんだ
continues forever.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Even higher, with a louder voice!
Prism Melody
聞こえてた？ 何かが始まるサイン
Could you hear it? The sign that something is starting.
集まって気付けば 和音(コード)を奏でた
When we gathered, we found ourselves playing a harmony.
夢に見るだけじゃもう 足りないでしょう
Just dreaming isn't enough anymore, is it?
君を待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you.
楽しい予感にほら 飛び乗っちゃえばいい
Look, just hop onto that fun intuition.
ときめきは止められないから
Because this excitement can't be stopped.
走ろう
Let's run.
連れて行くよ 光の真ん中
I'll take you to the center of the light.
夢の先へ 羽ばたける
We can fly toward the future of our dreams.
勇気は君の願い
Courage is your wish.
みんなで繋いだ この奇跡が
This miracle we all connected together...
途切れないように歌うんだ
let's sing so it never breaks.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Even higher, with a louder voice!
応えとか 理屈に惑わされて
Confused by answers and logic...
彷徨っても戻ってこれる場所があったんだ
I had a place to return to even when wandering.
自由自在 道行く僕らの旅
Our free-spirited journey...
願いだけが道標だよ
our wishes are the only guide.
夢の色が変わっても
Even if the colors of our dreams change...
変わらないメロディ
the melody stays the same.
君のために 僕らのために
For you, and for us...
歌おう
Let's sing.
そうさ きっと僕らの奇跡は
Yes, surely our miracle...
終わらないよ 涙さえ
will never end, even tears...
きっかけに変えていこう
we'll turn into a catalyst.
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に
Along with friends who believe...
どこへだって飛び出して行こう
let's head out anywhere.
もっと 遠く 空へ
Even further, into the sky!
いくよ！
Here we go!
未来の僕らに
To us in the future,
まだ見ぬ君に
to you whom we've yet to see,
伝えたいこと
there are so many things
たくさんあるんだ
I want to tell you.
迎えたいまは
This moment we've reached
当たり前なんかじゃない
isn't something to take for granted.
翼を広げさあ今
Spread your wings and now,
飛ぼう
let's fly.
Take my hand
連れていくよ
I'll take you away
光の真ん中
to the middle of the light,
夢の先へ
beyond our dreams.
羽ばたける
The courage to take flight
勇気は君の願い
is your wish.
みんなで繋いでいこう
Let's all stay connected,
この奇跡が
so this miracle
途切れないように歌うんだ
will never end, I'll sing it.
もっと高く！大きな声で
Higher! With a louder voice,
僕らの未来まで
even to our future,
どこまでも響け
echo everywhere,
Prism Melody
Show Them (Who You Are)
Won’t you just forget about the past?
Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had, I’m hoping it will last
Bersama kita t’lah lewati
Together we've passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
laughter and joy becoming memories.
Pastikan artinya ‘kan cerahkanmu nanti
Ensure that the meaning will brighten you later.
You were meant to do
More in time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Gunung dan mimpi yang kau layangkan kau cari
Mountains and dreams that you fly, you seek,
Teriakkan
Scream it out.
La la la la la la la la
Pastikan sendiri
Ensure it yourself.
It’s time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t’lah lewati
Together we've passed through
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
laughter and joy becoming memories.
Pastikan artinya ‘kan cerahkanmu nanti
Ensure that the meaning will brighten you later.
Cerahkanmu nanti
Brighten you later.
You were meant to do
More in time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Gunung dan mimpi yang kau layangkan kau cari
Mountains and dreams that you fly, you seek,
Teriakkan
Scream it out.
La la la la la la la la
Pastikan sendiri
Ensure it yourself.
Go go go
Terbanglah tinggi
Fly high,
Terbang dan tunjukkan siapa dirimu
fly and show who you are.
I will be singing it
La la la la la la la la
Be who you meant to be
頑張ろー！
Let's do our best!
Takkan takut tuk melangkah
I won't be afraid to take a step
Jauh melampaui batas
Far beyond the limits
Akhirnya semua kan baik saja
Finally, everything will be alright
Arahkan pandanganmu
Set your sights
Tajam lurus ke depan
Sharply straight ahead
Tuk meraih mimpi
To reach your dreams
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Grasp what you seek
Takkan lelah la la la la la la la la
I won't get tired la la la...
Hadapi sendiri
Facing it alone
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing la la la la la la la la
I'll be singing la la la...
Takkan hadapi sendiri
I won't face it alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go oh
Just look around and see, it's so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment I can dream with you
Every miracle we hope for might come true
We come together reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly you're here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We're on our way to good times, goodbye!
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one!
Setting things in motion,
get up and start a celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom zoom zoom, my heart goes boom boom boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud loud loud, our time is right now
We're here together finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
Hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear
So glad to be here together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times, goodbye!
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Raise up your hands and sway
Your light will lead our way
We're shining all for one, all for one!
Stamping your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road
Feel the music in your passion and soul
We're with you right now, so let the good times roll
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite
We're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one
Let's sing! All for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one
We're on our way to good times, goodbye!
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for
The dream we're striving toward
We're singing all for one, all for one!
皆さん、あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
おめでとう！
Happy New Year!
Reach to the top, we are ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブDEV_ISコラボステージです。
聴いてください、「FG ROADSTER」、by ReGLOSS！
From here, it's the hololive DEV_IS collab stage.
Please listen to "FG ROADSTER" by ReGLOSS!
Let's go!
搭載 V8 エンジン
Powered by a V8 engine
第七感持ってる源泉
The source of a seventh sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Locking down this world and all of humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
This group of five will change the game
うなる 4WD 8000
Roaring 4WD, 8000
皆さん サンキュー 散漫 3.14
Everyone, thank you, scattered 3.14
相対 2台のタンデム
Two relative tandems
獲る一番ここからゼロ
Taking number one, from zero right here
リミッター超えて頂点
Beyond the limiter, to the peak
チャンスもセットだ当然
Naturally, a chance is included
登り上げる頂点
Climbing up to the summit
ポップに飛んでく SHOWTIME
A pop-filled SHOWTIME taking off
乗り込め FG ROADSTER
Jump into the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊 集合 能力者
Special forces assemble, gifted ones
この歴史に名を放つ
Let our names ring through history
ぶっちぎりで置き去り 降伏しろ
Leaving you in the dust, just surrender
今 高速で ぶち抜いていく体験
Experiencing breaking through at high speed now
エンジンからジェットの炎 揺れている快適
Jet flames from the engine, a shaking comfort
先行 広がる大地を越えていく快適
Crossing the spreading earth, a comfortable ride
バックミラーに ビッグブルーが映ってる IBM
Big Blue in the rearview mirror, IBM
FIRE!
ぶち上げたいから 飛んでくうならせた
Wanting to fire it up, I made it roar
この道 果てないぜ 銀河にスリップストリーム
This road is endless, slipstreaming the galaxy
見えてるデカいビジョン 燃えてるメンバー一同
Seeing a huge vision, all the members are burning
ただいま 現在 進行形 超えてく 世界規模
Right now, in progress, going beyond global scale
鳴らすハスラー ワンステップ
Sounding the hustler, one step
心臓がモンスターエリア
My heart is a monster area
足りない FG パーリナイ
Not enough, FG party night
光るディスクローター
Shining disc rotor
ヘビーブースター 目覚めていく本能
Heavy booster, instinct awakening
青い炎
Blue flames
BMS Let's go out
届け銀河 ゼロから
Reach the galaxy, from zero
宇宙まで 囚われず 走る FG ROADSTER
To the edge of space, unrestrained, racing FG ROADSTER
うなるブースター
Roaring booster
ログ残せ It's me
Leave a log, it's me
今 チェイスミー
Chase me now
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私たち FLOW GLOW が、
ReGLOSS先輩の「フィーリングラデーション」をかまさせていただきます！
From here, we FLOW GLOW will perform
ReGLOSS-senpai's "feelingradation"!
ニコタンが来たー！
Niko-tan is here!
セクシーに行くぞ、しょっぴしょま！
Going sexy, shoppishoma!
ホロライブDEV_IS、レッツゴー！頑張るぞー！
hololive DEV_IS, let's go! Let's do our best!
シビれさせちゃうぞ、ビビ！
I'm gonna make you tingle, Vivi!
私たちの音に来い！
Come to our sound!
My heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
The new chapter I've unraveled
様変わりしていく show time
Show time is changing
全然悪くない イマジネーション
It's not bad at all, imagination
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in my field of vision clears up
悲しみに別れを告げる
Saying goodbye to sadness
酸いも甘いも 宙に放りだして
Throwing the sweet and sour into the sky
滲む空インクはバラ色
The ink in the bleeding sky is rose-colored
どれだけうまく見せようとしても
No matter how well I try to show it
君がいなければ 何の意味もない
It means nothing if you're not here
かすり傷すらつかない幻想
A fantasy where not even a scratch remains
針の落ちない レコードのさ
Like a record where the needle won't drop
赤い瞳 ドレミファ色を風にして
Red eyes, making the Do-Re-Mi colors into the wind
Come on, let's rock
颯爽と吹き荒れる向かい風にも心
Even in the dashing headwind, my heart...
なびかせて
will flutter.
飛び出せ to the future
Fly out to the future
ライジングしたって終わりたくはない Hey!
Even after rising, I don't want it to end, Hey!
ときめき仕舞えば
If I tuck away the excitement
瞬く間に広がる解放
Liberation spreads in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ全てがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama
待ちわびた デベリスタライフ Hey!
The long-awaited DEV_IS-style life, Hey!
変わりゆく色のパノラマ
A panorama of changing colors
満ち溢れる フィーリングラデーション
Overflowing with feelingradation
飛び出して You make me up
Fly out, you make me up
恐れるものはない デベリスタライフ Hey!
There's nothing to fear, DEV_IS-style life, Hey!
綺麗ださ 夜明けが
The dawn is so beautiful
透明な明日を照らすよ
Illuminating the transparent tomorrow
デベリスタライフ Hey!
DEV_IS-style life, Hey!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最後の曲は、「Our Bright Parade」！
The final song is "Our Bright Parade"!
Parade, parade, parade!
パレ、パレ、パレ
Parade, parade, parade
輝くんだよ
Shine bright
呼び合う声を合図に
With the voices calling to each other as a signal
Our Bright Parade
パレパレパレ
Pare-pare-pare
探しに行く
Going to search for it
スタートは 何度だって
The start can be any number of times
ただ 独り言 続いた
Just a monologue that continued
ただ 始まりたくて 走った
Just wanting to start, I ran
遠く 暮れた灯りに灯った
In the distant darkness, a light flickered
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name that was too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思い出
That was a memory that was too kind
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get even closer
思いがけず 結び合った
Unexpectedly, we were tied together
ほら 今 迷い子は 僕らになった
Look, now we've become the lost children
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Pare-pare-pare, it's shining
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring your frustrations and your affection along
風 夢 羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer is the light
終わりなき日差し
The endless sunshine
君を 見つけたこと
Having found you...
胸を 張れるよ
I can be proud of it
ここから これから
From here, from now on
Our Bright Parade-Pare
まだ 頼りない横顔
Still a profile I can't rely on
歌を 恥ずかしくなって 泣いた
I cried because the song became embarrassing
誰も 解けぬ火 魔法に
To the magic of a fire no one can extinguish
いつか また会える おまじない
A lucky charm so we can meet again someday
あの日 手のひら 始まった
Starting on that day, in my palm
ストーリー
Story
数え切れない言の葉
Countless words
数えるような思いじゃないさ
It's not a feeling you can count
ほら 今 僕らを 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let's call us one
パレパレパレ 美しいんだよ
Pare-pare-pare, it's beautiful
許しあえる せつな 夜は煌めく
Forgive each other, for a moment the night sparkles
雨 晴れ パレ 跨いだ空
Rain, shine, parade, the sky we crossed
ふさわしい旅路とは
The suitable journey is...
君と歩くことさ
walking with you.
君と歩くことなんだ
It's about walking with you.
ただいまを聞けば
If I hear 'I'm home,'
おかえりって叫ぶよ
I'll shout 'Welcome back!'
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't it obvious?
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Pare-pare-pare, it's shining
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ
Filling the darkness is you and me
パレパレパレ 輝くんだよ
Pare-pare-pare, it's shining
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring your frustrations and your affection along
風 夢 羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings, we can take flight
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer is the light
終わりなき日差し
The endless sunshine
君と 飛び込んでいく
I'll dive in with you
素敵な スタートさ
It's a wonderful start
ここから これから
From here, from now on
Our Bright Parade-Pare
Our Bright Parade-Pare!
キャスト
Cast
セットリスト
Setlist
「RENEGADE」
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame, Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen, Raora Panthera
"RENEGADE"
「アワータイムイエロー」
音乃瀬奏, 一条莉々華, 儒烏風亭らでん, 轟はじめ
"Our Time Yellow"
Otonose Kanade, Ichijou Ririka, Juufuutei Raden, Todoroki Hajime
「Genesis」
Shiori Novella, Koseki Bijou, Nerissa Ravencroft, Fuwawa Abyssgard, Mococo Abyssgard
"Genesis"
「id:entity voices」
Vestia Zeta, Kobo Kanaeru
"id:entity voices"
「暁闇エクステス」
ラプラス・ダークネス, 鷹嶺ルイ, 博衣こより, 沙花叉クロヱ, 風真いろは
"Twilight Exodus"
La+ Darknesss, Takane Lui, Hakui Koyori, Sakamata Chloe, Kazama Iroha
「Run Back 'Round」
IRyS, Ouro Kronii, Hakos Baelz
"Run Back 'Round"
「Slap by Step」
Kureiji Ollie, Anya Melfissa, Pavolia Reine
"Slap by Step"
「Fortune Spinner」
Mori Calliope, Takanashi Kiara, Ninomae Ina'nis
"Fortune Spinner"
「Hyper Jumpin'」
雪花ラミィ, 桃鈴ねね, 獅白ぼたん, 尾丸ポルカ
"Hyper Jumpin'"
Yukihana Lamy, Momosuzu Nene, Shishiro Botan, Omaru Polka
「Dramatic XViltration」
Ayunda Risu, Moona Hoshinova, Airani Iofifteen
"Dramatic XViltration"
「青春アーカイブ」
角巻わため, 常闇トワ
"Seishun Archive"
Tsunomaki Watame, Tokoyami Towa
「夢見る空へ」
兎田ぺこら, 不知火フレア, 白銀ノエル, 宝鐘マリン
"Yumemiru Sora e"
Usada Pekora, Shiranui Flare, Shirogane Noel, Houshou Marine
「We are GAMERS !!!!」
白上フブキ, 大神ミオ, 猫又おかゆ, 戌神ころね
"We are GAMERS !!!!"
Shirakami Fubuki, Ookami Mio, Nekomata Okayu, Inugami Korone
「キラメキライダー☆」
百鬼あやめ, 癒月ちょこ, 大空スバル
"Kirameki Rider☆"
Nakiri Ayame, Yuzuki Choco, Oozora Subaru
「電脳ぴゅあお推し大宣言」
アキ・ローゼンタール, 赤井はあと, 白上フブキ, 夏色まつり
"Cyber Pure Oshi Grand Declaration"
Aki Rosenthal, Akai Haato, Shirakami Fubuki, Natsuiro Matsuri
「Shiny Smily Story」
ときのそら, ロボ子さん, AZKi, さくらみこ
"Shiny Smily Story"
Tokino Sora, Roboco, AZKi, Sakura Miko
「Prism Melody」
"Prism Melody"
「Show Them (Who You Are)」
Ayunda Risu, Moona Hoshinova, Airani Iofifteen, Kureiji Ollie, Anya Melfissa, Pavolia Reine, Vestia Zeta, Kobo Kanaeru
"Show Them (Who You Are)"
「All for One」
Mori Calliope, Takanashi Kiara, Ninomae Ina'nis, IRyS, Ouro Kronii, Hakos Baelz, Shiori Novella, Koseki Bijou, Nerissa Ravencroft, Fuwawa Abyssgard, Mococo Abyssgard, Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame, Gigi Murin, Cecilia Immergreen, Raora Panthera
"All for One"
「DEV_IS COUNTDOWN メドレー2025」
音乃瀬奏, 一条莉々華, 儒烏風亭らでん, 轟はじめ, 瑞流リナオ, 虎金妃笑虎, 水宮枢, 輪堂千速, 緋々良々ヴィヴィ
"DEV_IS COUNTDOWN Medley 2025"
Otonose Kanade, Ichijou Ririka, Juufuutei Raden, Todoroki Hajime, Mizuryu Linao, Koganebi Nico, Mizumiya Su, Rindo Chihaya, Hibara Vivi
「Our Bright Parade」
ときのそら, ロボ子さん, AZKi, さくらみこ, アキ・ローゼンタール, 赤井はあと, 白上フブキ, 夏色まつり, 百鬼あやめ, 癒月ちょこ, 大空スバル, 大神ミオ, 猫又おかゆ, 戌神ころね
"Our Bright Parade"
Tokino Sora, Roboco, AZKi, Sakura Miko, Aki Rosenthal, Akai Haato, Shirakami Fubuki, Natsuiro Matsuri, Nakiri Ayame, Yuzuki Choco, Oozora Subaru, Ookami Mio, Nekomata Okayu, Inugami Korone
この後は もう1本グランプリ！
2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Next up: Another Grand Prix!
Thank you for supporting hololive production in 2026!